Dezas! Ești bine?!
Da. Evilbarrow e în siguranță.
And three strong magic forces have
vanished from the battlefield,
presumably Toma's minions.
Now the tide of the battle
should turn in our favor.
Good. Seeing how Setsu made it
in time, we should be able to—
You thought things would change, huh?
Long time no see.
I guess the last time was five years ago,
at the peace ceremony.
No matter which way the tides of battle go,
the end will be the same.
Because I'm here.
Now, it's the beginning of the end.
Do try to resist. I'll teach you what despair is.
Episodul 12
Luptând pentru a doua oară bătălia finală
Dezas! Levia!
Setsu...
Hey, Setsu. That was fast.
I knew you'd come, but it still makes
me jealous to see you actually show up.
Toma, you...
Since I'm going to kill them anyway,
I thought the least I could do is—
Like hell I'm gonna let you do that.
I knew my Setsu would say that.
I guess there's no point
in talking to you anymore.
You're right. Once the world
ends and we're alone,
we'll have plenty of time to talk.
Still quite a brute, aren't you?
Here we go!
The sky... cracked?!
They're on a whole different level.
Are you done warming up?
Yeah. Let's fight for real now.
What is this, strength in numbers?!
Flying Sword!
Damn it!
You're wide open!
Flying Sword, Zetsu!
Oh? Have you lost your touch?
Heh, keep talking!
I like that look on your face.
I let my guard down.
I forgot that you're a tricky fighter.
I know neither of us wants to drag this out.
Let's up the pace.
What is that?
Form Change.
A new possibility for my sacred sword.
Let's go to stage two!
Seriously?
I can't let him start shooting
that thing everywhere.
Shot!
Damn it!
I guess it's not that easy to land a hit.
Seriously?!
Damn it! Come, Glutton!
Devour it!
Setsu's sacred sword!
That scary sword of yours
really is a nuisance.
I'm starting to think it looks kinda cool.
Yuki-kun!
Setsu!
Yeah!
Looks like you're all safe.
All of your friends are gone.
Why don't you call it quits now, Toma?
S-Setsu...
You're always... always...
You're always leaving me alone! Only me!
This power...
It's not coming from Toma!
So that's what it is!
Let's settle everything
once and for all, Setsu!
I'll show you the power I can
gain by sacrificing my life!
What is that?!
I've never seen magic power like that before!
Limit Break...
Let's end this, Setsu.
Let's stop despair from spreading
any further across this world.
He's out of control!
What's wrong?!
There's no way my Setsu can do nothing
but run away like a scared little mouse!
Damn it! I can't get close to him!
How is anyone supposed to fight that?
We can't count on it running
out of ammo, either.
You're amazing, Setsu!
But what will you do about this?!
What the...
Too late.
Open your mouth, Glutton!
No!
You useless pieces of trash!
It's all...
Now it's my turn, Toma!
Where is he?!
I'm here!
Flying Sword! Rapid Fire!
What is that move?!
This ends now, Toma!
I...
Setsu. My name is Setsu.
We're the only allies we've got,
since we come from the same place.
You can stop calling me "-san."
I am...
Let's stop this war.
So I'll protect you.
Yeah, let's meet again once we've
both become heroes for real.
I am...
Toma the Hero!
Toma-sama!
Of course, Toma-sama.
Toma-sama.
Toma-sama!
That's a promise.
That's a promise, Setsu.
Yeah, it's a promise.
Seriously?
Damn it!
Damn it...
Setsu?
I won?
I beat Setsu?!
The same Setsu who was always
ahead of me in every way?!
I knew I was right!
This world did need to be destroyed!
You did indeed get a lot stronger.
But until you regain the things
that were precious to you...
No matter how strong you get,
you'll never beat me.
Dimensional magic?! How do you
still have the strength to use this?!
If you can do it, I can do it too, obviously.
L-Limit Break?!
Open your mouth even wider!
Earth Eater!
N-No!
I don't want to die!
I don't want to die! I don't want
to die! I don't want to die!
I don't want to die alone! No!
Hey, Setsu? Didn't you promise
that you'd protect me?
That's why I tried to stay by your side...
Hey... Setsu... Setsu!
Setsu! Setsu! Setsu!
I see now.
All I really wanted was...
to be by Setsu's side.
Am I...
Hey, you're awake.
Why...
Us killing each other was never my goal.
I wanted to bring you back
to your senses somehow.
So I took a gamble on letting my sword
eat only the curse cast on you.
Besides, I promised I'd protect you, right?
But... I did so many unforgivable things...
Why...
So you can atone for what you've done.
No matter how long it takes.
I won't allow you to just die
and let it all end there.
I knew I couldn't beat you, Setsu.
Setsu! You okay?!
Hey!
Ow, that hurts! Don't touch me!
Cleaning this up is gonna be a lot of work...
They've decided what to do with you.
I see. That was faster than I thought.
Use all of your magic
power on a transfer spell.
Send my classmates back
to their original world.
That's your punishment.
What? That's it?
Without your magic power,
you're just a regular human.
You won't be able to do anything bad.
In that case, we don't care about you.
Given the look on your face, you don't
intend to do anything wrong, anyway!
So you should just go with them.
I'm sure you can start over, right?
Setsu...
So that's that. I'm counting on you, Toma.
You should thank Setsu for
negotiating this outcome.
We're only doing this because Setsu asked.
You'll keep every promise,
even the ones you made with me, Setsu?
Now you can go back to your original world.
All right!
Okay, you guys, take care.
See ya! Goodbye!
You're sure you didn't want
to go back with them?
My true atonement starts now.
I'm going to go on a trip.
I'll see this world with my own eyes
and think about what I can do for it.
Just like you did.
Sounds good. I'll be rooting for you.
See you again, Setsu.
Yeah, later.
Right, well, see ya!
I really want to go with you! Please!
No. There's too much post-war
paperwork to deal with.
Given our positions, we can't get out of it.
I don't wanna be a knight anymore!
I'm here.
Sorry to make you wait.
This is going to be a pretty
aimless trip. Are you sure?
Yes. I've decided to always stay at your side.
Yeah? Okay, then.
Thanks.
Sure!
Well, time to finally enjoy
my relaxed other world life.
See ya!
You sure about this, Elka?
I am Setsu-sama's sword.
And his chair. That's fine.
Hey!
Levia!
Are the seas safe?
Setsu!
Of course the seas are eternally
at peace, as long as I'm around!
That's great! You're incredible, Levia-san!
Naturally! I've known Setsu for
much longer than you have, and—
What's the matter with you?!
Ow! Suction! Suction hurts!
You stupid soft-bodied monster!
Make it so.
Yes, my lord!
Dezas.
Setsu!
Looks like the demonic
nation is recovering well.
Yes, I'm blessed with great officers.
This damage will be repaired
before you know it.
Oh, Ruri is doing well in her own shop, too.
Heroic Squid Rings and Fried Octopus!
The end of the line is over here.
One squid ring, please!
Me, too! Hey, don't push!
Wow.
They're so popular!
An invention by the hero who saved the world!
They're crunchy and delicious! Have a bite!
Yay, squid rings! I want one, too!
I had to thank her for
delivering my precious brooch.
I'm glad I provided her
with the best location.
I'm telling you, I know Regulus!
Haven't we been through this already?!
Setsu!
Check this out, Setsu!
I'm the commander of the army of
Zoo Dorado, Roa Leonaire! Cool, huh?
Deputy Commander Shironeko here.
Second Deputy, Mineko.
The three of us are training super hard!
We'll beat you one day, Setsu!
Just you wait!
Seems like the Beastmen nation is okay, too.
I'm glad we have a new
generation of fine warriors!
Uimitor...
E așa de frumos!
Această lume e plină
de lucruri minunate.
Da!